ponomusic.com 2018-09-07

# PonoMusic | Store

### PONOMUSIC PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to PonoMusic! Ivanhoe (DE) Inc., a Delaware corporation dba Pono Music (“PONO” or “we” or “us”) has created this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) in order to demonstrate its commitment to user, visitor, subscriber, and customer privacy with regard to the website located at www.PonoMusic.com and other websites provided by PONO (collectively the “Website”).

Privacy on the Website is of great importance to us. Because we may gather some important information from our users, visitors, subscribers and customers (collectively “Subscribers” or “you” or “your”), we have established this Privacy Policy as a means to communicate how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. By accessing the Website, you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Policy and also agree to the Terms and Conditions of Use, which can be accessed and reviewed at eula.ponomusic.com.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may require users who use the Website or who purchase products or use services offered through the Website (collectively, the “Service”) to give us contact information, which may include but is not limited to the users’ name, mailing address, phone number, email address, date of birth, gender and other personal information about you. In addition to information voluntarily provided by you, we may also automatically collect other information regarding your use of the Website. All information that you voluntarily provide to PONO and that we automatically collect will be referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Personal Information”, including but not limited to Internet protocol addresses used by you to connect your computer or other device to the Internet. You can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it or not using the Website, although not providing it may hinder your ability to use the Website and/or the Service.

We use the information that we collect to provide and maintain the Website as we deem appropriate in our sole discretion and to provide the Service, and to provide any other services at PONO’s sole and absolute discretion. However, at all times, unless PONO obtains your express consent, we will use the information we collect only in a manner that you would reasonably expect from using the Service. 

We may also use the Personal Information to contact you to further discuss interest in our company, the goods and services that we provide, and to send information, including marketing, promotions, events and contents correspondences, regarding our company or partners

You may be invited to receive an email newsletter or other correspondence related to the Service by providing an email address. Your email address and any Personal Information will not be distributed or shared with third parties (1. unless it is to transact such business as you have contracted us to do, (including third parties for the purposes of credit card verification), to comply with any legal processes and/or law enforcement requests, or in order to conduct any business as we, in our sole subjective discretion, deem reasonable.

We may also email (or send via other methods) information regarding updates to the Website or PONO, and may send a newsletter, or other correspondence. You will have an opportunity to unsubscribe to any emails or mailings by clicking on an “unsubscribe” hyperlink contained in promotional emails we send you. Even if you are removed from any such list, if you use the Service, you will continue to receive email correspondence from PONO related to the Service. Any opt-out by you is not deemed valid until processed by PONO. It is your obligation to verify that you have been opted-out. PONO shall not be liable for problems with the opt-out procedures.

If you provide credit card or other authorized payment method information in the course of purchasing goods or services through the Website, you authorize PONO’s credit card processor(s), some of which may be located outside of your home jurisdiction, to receive appropriate billing information, bill such credit card and/or to make such charges as applicable. 

PONO does not wish to collect any Personal Information (or any information at all) from any persons under 14 years old. If you are under 14 years old, you may not use the Website.

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

The Website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. You will need to check the policy statement of these others websites to understand their policies. When you access a linked site you may be disclosing private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential. PONO is not responsible for any private information, including but not limited to Personal Information disclosed by you to such other third party websites.

**COOKIES**

We may use data collection devices such as “cookies” (small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes) and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons to assist us in providing our services. These technologies make using the Website easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you, helping identify you whenever you return to our Website, and reducing the number of times you are required to enter your password during a session. These technologies can also help us provide information that is targeted toward your interests and preferences. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent (note: you may need to consult your browser’s “Help” area for instructions). If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session. Please note, that if you set your browser to block acceptance of cookies, this may affect your ability to use the Service or certain portions of the Website.

Cookies will not be used by PONO to gather specific personal information about individual users. The usage patterns tracked by individual cookies will remain confidential, and PONO will not participate in any external site tracking programs, nor will we share any cookie-generated information about individual users or user patterns.

**USER IP ADDRESSES**

PONO tracks user IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration, demographic profiling and traffic logging, but PONO will not use IP addresses to try to identify individual users of the Website.

**SECURITY**

Please note that data that is transported over an open network, such as the Internet or e-mail, may be accessible to anybody. We cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted via such open networks. When disclosing any personal information via an open network, you should remain mindful of the fact that it is potentially accessible to others, and consequently, can be collected and used by others without your consent. In particular, while individual data packets are often encrypted, the names of the sender and recipient are not. A third party may therefore be able to trace an existing bank account or relationship or one that is subsequently created. Even if both the sender and recipient are located in the same country, data may also be transmitted via such networks to other countries regularly and without controls, including to countries that do not afford the same level of data protection as your country of domicile.

Your data may be lost during transmission or may be accessed by unauthorized parties. We do not accept, and expressly disclaim, any liability for direct or indirect losses arising out of any breaches of security in any way pertaining to your Personal Information or any other data during its transfer via the Internet. Please use other means of communication if you think this is necessary or prudent for security reasons.

Personal data collected by PONO may be transferred across provincial, state and/or international borders and stored in jurisdictions outside of your home jurisdiction. These receiving jurisdictions may be subject to different standards of privacy protection than apply in your home jurisdiction.

PONO maintains record retention and destruction policies that govern how long information will be stored by PONO and when that information will be destroyed. Personal information will be destroyed by PONO when it is no longer required by law to retain the information, and when it is no longer required for any of the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy. You may at any time have all personal information about you destroyed by emailing support@ponomusic.com.

**ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website and any use of the Website is governed by those Terms and Conditions of Use. Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of the Website should be directed to PONO by emailing such questions to support@ponomusic.com.

**UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

PONO reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, and such changes will be effective upon being posted herein. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then current Privacy Policy because it is binding on you. Your continued use of the Website after any such changes and/or postings shall constitute your consent to such changes.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact our Customer Service Department at support@ponomusic.com.

**CALIFORNIA DO-NOT-TRACK DISCLOSURES**

PONO does not track your use of the Website over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, your browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked.

**PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California Civil Code § 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of their personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, or to inquire about PONO’s compliance with its privacy obligations and/or to obtain information regarding PONO’s privacy policies and practices please send e-mail to support@ponomusic.com or write us at:

PONO Privacy Rights   
1501 Mariposa St   
Suite 312   
San Francisco CA 94107

11202015PMPP
